https://lrus.wolterskluwer.com/store/tax-essentials/?in_type=banner-image&in_name=legalmarketsegmentdrop

Loading...
About Us
We know your business is rapidly adapting to the global COVID-19 outbreak.
If you need assistance with your Wolters Kluwer products or would like to get more information on a complimentary Guest Pass to any of our online products,
please contact your representative. To help you stay informed and navigate the changes, Wolters Kluwer is providing free insights and resources. View Resources here >>
Close
Legal
Securities & Corporate Law
Intellectual Property
Antitrust & Competition
Banking & Consumer Finance Law
Elder & Estate Law
Family Law
View All Practice Areas
Request a demo today!
Corporate
Pension
Employee Benefits
Labor & Employment Law
Government Contracts
Corporate Counsel
Payroll & Entitlements
Human Resources
View All Practice Areas
Request a demo today!
Government
Government Contracts
Antitrust, Competition Law & Trade
Transportation Law
Labor & Employment Law
Securities & Corporate Law
Energy
View All Practice Areas
Tax Essentials
Spend less time searching and more time addressing your clients’ needs. Leading tax practitioners provide a new, continuously curated, topically arranged 360-degree view of more than 1,000 Federal, State, and International tax issues.
Request Demo
Call us today at 1-800-955-5217
Need help?
Overview
Related Products
Overview
Get the answers you need faster and with greater accuracy than ever before.Access comprehensive Primary and Secondary content, tools, Client Letters, Smart Charts, Practice Aids, and forms – all in one seamless, intuitive experience. More than 1,000 key Federal, State, and International tax topics are continuously curated and topically arranged so that a 360-degree view of a tax issue is never more than two clicks away.
Stay a step ahead.Industry experts and leading tax practitioners provide the most extensive, up-to-date information possible.
Authors include:
Anthony J. Nitti, CPA, MST Tax Partner, Withum Smith & Brown, PC
Andrew E. Mitchell, J.D., Mitchell Law Group
Robert W. Jamison, CPA, PhD Indiana University
Take a Tour of Tax Essentials
Navigate with ease.Curated content is organized by topic and includes news, treaties, and primary sources to help your team stay informed for real scenarios.
Topics include:
Business Deductions and Credits
C Corporations
Estates, Gifts, and Trusts
Federal Tax Reform
International Taxation
Nonbusiness Deductions and Credits
Retirement Plans
S Corporations
Bonus Depreciation (State)
Nexus
Base Erosion and Profit Sharing (BEPS)
Get what you need more quickly.You’ll never be more than one or two clicks away from the comprehensive set of materials associated with a topic. You’ll find primary content, related tools, forms, Smart Charts, news and clients letters for more than 1,000 Federal, State and International topics.
Related Products
Cheetah ™ Tax Law
Tax Reporters Plus Suite
To proceed, please Log In or Create an Account
I have an account
I'm new here
Please enter the email address and password used at registration.
Your account is locked due to too many failed login attempts. Please wait 30 minutes and try again or click “Forgot Password"
Email Address
This email address is not registered.
Please enter your Email Address
The email address you entered is not valid
Password
Please enter a Password
Your password must be at least 6 characters long
No validation was done for leading or trailing spaces in password.
Login
Forgot Password?
Remember me
First Name
Please enter your First Name
Last Name
Please enter your Last Name
Country of Residence
Please select Country Of Residence
Email Address
This email address is already in use.
Forgot Password?
Please enter your Email Address
The email address you entered is not valid
Create a Password
Please enter a Password
Your password must be at least 6 characters long
No validation was done for leading or trailing spaces in password.
Yes, I would like to create an account.
I consent to the collection of my personal information by Wolters Kluwer Legal & Regulatory U.S., operated through CCH Incorporated and its affiliate Kluwer Law International, so that I can create an account to store my contact information and order history to facilitate ecommerce transactions.
I understand that my personal information will be processed for this purpose in the United States where CCH Incorporated operates.
You may change or withdraw your consent at any time by contacting our Customer Service team at +1-301-698-7100 or [email protected].
For more information about our privacy practices, please refer to our privacy statement: www.WoltersKluwerLR.com/privacy.
Online subscription product purchases require that you create an account.
Invalid captcha. Please enter correct captcha.
Register
Remember me
Browse PRACTICE AREAS
A-Z
Antitrust & Competition
Antitrust, Competition Law & Trade
Arbitration, Dispute Resolution & Mediation
Banking & Consumer Finance Law
Bankruptcy
Blue Chip
Comparative Law
(International)
Comparative Law
(Legal)
Competition Law
Construction Law
Corporate Counsel
Cybersecurity & Privacy
Elder & Estate Law
Employee Benefits
(Corporate)
Employee Benefits
(Legal)
Energy
(Corporate)
Energy
(Government)
Environmental
European Union Law
Family Law
Government Contracts
(Corporate)
Government Contracts
(Government)
Health Law
Health Law & Administration
Healthcare Coding & Reimbursement
Healthcare Compliance Management
Healthcare Incident Management
Healthcare Policy Management
Healthcare Regulatory Change Management
Healthcare Risk Assessment & Mitigation
Labor & Employment Law
(Corporate)
Labor & Employment Law
(Government)
Labor & Employment Law
(Legal)
Litigation
Payroll & Entitlements
Pension
(Corporate)
Pension
(Legal)
Practice of Law
Products Liability
Real Estate
Securities & Corporate Law
(Government)
Securities & Corporate Law
(Legal)
Survey, Attest, & Engage
Tax Law
Telecommunications
Transportation Law
To proceed, please Log In or Create an Account
I have an account
I'm new here
Please enter the email address and password used at registration.
Your account is locked due to too many failed login attempts. Please wait 30 minutes and try again or click “Forgot Password"
Email Address
This email address is not registered.
Please enter your Email Address
The email address you entered is not valid
Password
Please enter a Password
Your password must be at least 6 characters long
No validation was done for leading or trailing spaces in password.
Login
Forgot Password?
Remember me
First Name
Please enter your First Name
Last Name
Please enter your Last Name
Country of Residence
Please select Country Of Residence
Email Address
This email address is already in use.
Forgot Password?
Please enter your Email Address
The email address you entered is not valid
Create a Password
Please enter a Password
Your password must be at least 6 characters long
No validation was done for leading or trailing spaces in password.
Yes, I would like to create an account.
I consent to the collection of my personal information by Wolters Kluwer Legal & Regulatory U.S., operated through CCH Incorporated and its affiliate Kluwer Law International, so that I can create an account to store my contact information and order history to facilitate ecommerce transactions.
I understand that my personal information will be processed for this purpose in the United States where CCH Incorporated operates.
You may change or withdraw your consent at any time by contacting our Customer Service team at +1-301-698-7100 or [email protected].
For more information about our privacy practices, please refer to our privacy statement: www.WoltersKluwerLR.com/privacy.
Online subscription product purchases require that you create an account.
Invalid captcha. Please enter correct captcha.
Register
Remember me
Request a Demo
Thank you for your interest in a free demo! We look forward to connecting with you.
Yes, send me information on similar products and content from Wolters Kluwer.
I consent to the collection of my personal information by Wolters Kluwer Legal & Regulatory U.S., operated through CCH Incorporated and its affiliate Kluwer Law International, so that I can be contacted about similar product(s) and content.
I understand that my personal information will be processed for this purpose in the United States where CCH Incorporated operates. Additionally, if the products being inquired about are fulfilled by Kluwer Law International, my personal information will be shared with Kluwer Law International and processed in the Netherlands or the United Kingdom where it operates.
You may change or withdraw your consent at any time by contacting our Customer Service team at +1-301-698-7100 or [email protected].
For more information about our privacy practices, please refer to our privacy statement: www.WoltersKluwerLR.com/privacy.
Submit
Thank you
One of our product experts will be in touch soon.
While you're at it, create an account.
Thank You.
Your request has been forwarded to a Wolters Kluwer representative who will contact you shortly!
Close
This Site Uses Cookies
By continuing to browse this site you are agreeing to our use of cookies.
Privacy Statement
Ok, I Understand
Information
Note that prices are displayed in the currency of your geographic location
Got it
Currency is not billing
